A Guide to the Margaret (Peggy) McGrath Rockefeller personal papers FA410
Rockefeller Archive Center
Margaret (Peggy) McGrath Rockefeller personal papers
1936-1996
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Peggy
FA410
41.98 Cubic Feet
Biographical / Historical
Margaret (Peggy) McGrath Rockefeller (1916-1996) was a dedicated conservationist and environmentalist. She was married to banking executive and philanthropist David Rockefeller.
In 1970, Peggy Rockefeller founded the Maine Coast Heritage Trust (MCHT) to protect and preserve areas of ecologic value across the state. During this time, she also began to purchase and raise pure-bred Simmental cattle in Maine on Bartlett Island and in Pocantico Hills, New York.
In 1980, she founded the American Farmland Trust, using her experience in farming to build programs that focused on national conservation easements.
Peggy Rockefeller was also highly involved with the New York Botanical Garden (NYBG), where she helped fund a collection of books on America's wildflowers. In 1988, the renowned Peggy Rockefeller Rose Garden at the NYBG opened in her honor. She was also an active member of the Nature Conservancy, National Trust for Historic Preservation, and the New York Philharmonic. She also regularly contributed to many art and conservation causes.
Scope and Contents
The Margaret (Peggy) McGrath Rockefeller personal papers consist of correspondence, personal files, and material related to various environmental and agricultural programs. The collection documents Peggy Rockefeller's activities in agriculture, farming, and conservation both in Maine and at her home in Pocantico Hills, New York. There is also a substantial amount of material related to the American Farmland Trust, Maine Coast Heritage Trust, and the New York Botanical Garden (NYGB).
Arrangement
The Margaret (Peggy) McGrath Rockefeller personal papers are arranged into four record groups, each representing a different accession.
Record Group 1: AC.2010.057: East 65th Street
Series 1: General Correspondence. Series 2: Topical Files which includes 11 subseries arranged by subject/category: Personal Files; Carriage Drives; Trips; Parties; Gardening and the New York Botanical Garden (NYBG); Art, Music, and Cattle; University of Pennsylvania and Rockefeller University; Conservation and Preservation; Maine; General Files; Maine Coast Heritage Trust (MCHT).
Record Group 2: AC.2011.004
Series 1: Personal Files. Series 2: Correspondence. Series 3: Bank and Engagement Books. Series 4: Photographs and Negatives.
Record Group 3: AC.2003.106: Apartment Files
Series 1: Personal Files. Series 2: Correspondence. Series 3: Maine Coast Heritage Trust (MCHT). Series 4: Environmental and Philanthropic Organizations. Series 5: Trips.
Record Group 4: AC.2005.030
Contains four files of letters relating to the McGrath family,including correspondence and publications relating to Peggy Rockefeller's parents.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Margaret (Peggy) McGrath Rockefeller papers were donated to the Rockefeller Archive Center by David Rockefeller in January 2011.
Separated Materials
Special format items have been separated from the body of the collection and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Conservation of natural resources -- Maine; Conservation of natural resources -- New York (State); Botanical gardens -- New York (State) -- New York (State); Maine; Cattle -- Breeding; Agriculture
- Accession 2010:057 - East 65th Street, 1946-1996; 1; 33.92 Cubic Feet 58 standard document boxes, 1 oversized flat box, and 7 record storage boxes
  - General Correspondence (East 65th Street), 1946-1996; 1; 15.7 Cubic Feet
    - Ackland, Mr. and Mrs. John (Rosemary) (Jessica - daughter), 1979-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Agnelli, Mr. and Mrs., Gianni (Marella), 1968-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Ahsan, Mr. and Mrs. Syed Akhtar (Sarwat), 1968-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Aldrich, Mr. and Mrs. Nelson ("Nel") (Frannie), 1961-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Aldrich, Elizabeth, 1986-1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Aldrich - Various, 1960-1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Ali, Mr. Syed Amjad, 1973-1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Allam, Mark Whittier, V.M.D., 1984-1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Allan, Mr. and Mrs. Albert (Mimi), 1984-1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Alsop, Dr. Reese, 1951-1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Amada, Kenneth, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Anderson, Mr. and Mrs. Arthur Forrest (Constance), 1967-1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Anderson, Col. and Mrs. John (Nancy), 1974-1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Anderson, Mr. and Mrs. Robert (Barbara), 1973-1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Andrade, Mr. and Mrs. Roberto (Megaly), 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Andrus III, John E., 1978 September-October (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Angst, Ethel, 1985-1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Annenberg, Mr. and Mrs. Walter (Leonore "Lee"), 1968-1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Armstrong, David, 1990 May-October (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Armstrong, Dr. and Mrs. James (Carol), 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Asphar, Judith, 1986-1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Astor, Mrs. Vincent (Brooke), 1973-1995 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Avery, Mr. and Mrs. John (Caron), 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Azcarrago, Mr. and Mrs. Emilio (Paula), 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - "A" Miscellaneous, 1989-1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Bagarotti, Mr. and Mrs. Giovanni (Cornelia), 1956-1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Ballantine, Arthur, 1965-1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Barber, Addie and Mamie, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Barber, Mrs. C.F. (Lois), 1991-1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Barnes, Mr. and Mrs. Edward (Mary), 1973-1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Barry, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Bass, Mr. and Mrs. Robert (Anne), 1985-1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Bass, Mr. and Mrs. Sid (Mercedes), 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Bates, Mr. and Mrs. Jake (Rita), 1988 January-May (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Beal, Mr. and Mrs. Clinton (Lottie), 1972-1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Beal, Mr. and Mrs. Elmer (Allison), 1973-1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Beard, Ronald, 1992 January-February (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Beatrix (Princess) and Claus (Prince), 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Behuniak, John, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Beltran, Mr. and Mrs. Pedro (Miriam), 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Bemiss, Mr. and Mrs. Fitzgerald ("Gerry")(Margaret), 1968 February-March (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Bendana, Mr. andMrs. Enrique (Cristina), 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Bender, Mr. and Mrs. David, 1973 February-June (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Bendetsen, Karl, 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Benedict, Stephen, 1968-1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Benson, Charles, 1979 March-December (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Berg, Kirsti, 1972 April-June (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Bergus, Mr. and Mrs. Donald (Liz), 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Bermann, Clara ("Tante Nancy"), 1947-1955 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Biddle, Mr. and Mrs. Charles (Phoebe), 1971-1988 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Binnewies, Mr. and Mrs. Robert (Midge), 1969-1995 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Bish, Mr. and Mrs. James (Elisabeth), 1973-1988 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Black, Peter, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Blagden, Mr. and Mrs. Allen (Kerry), 1971-1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Blair, Robert, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Blocker, Mr. and Mrs. Robert (Maritza), 1979 June-November (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Blum, Mr. and Mrs. Robert (Ethel), 1984-1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Blum, Mr. and Mrs. John (Jeannie) (Suzie - daughter), 1974-1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Blumenthal, Brad, 1990 October-November (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Boardman, Mr. and Mrs. William (Jane), 1974-1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Bolton, Mr. and Mrs. Robert (Marion), 1985-1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Bowditch, Mr. and Mrs. Nathaniel (Peggy), 1974-1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Bracho, Mr. and Mrs. Antonio (Teresa), 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Branson, John, 1985-1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Brengle, Laurence ("Jack"), 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Brewer-Carias, Dr. Charles, 1988 January-June (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Brewster, Mr. and Mrs. Klingman (Mary-Louise), 1973 February-March (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Brillembourg, Mr. and Mrs. Arturo (Clara), 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Bronk, Mr. and Mrs. Detley ("Det") (Helen), 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Brooke, Mrs. and Mrs. Piers (Susy), 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Browarny, Walt, 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Brune, Mr. and Mrs. William (Dosa), 1976-1990 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Bryan, Rov. Robert A., 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Bryant, Mr. and Mrs. Donald (Marg) (Peter, Peggy), 1965-1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Brzezinski, Mr. and Mrs. Zbigniew (Muska), 1973-1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Bullock, Richard, 1974-1980 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Bundy, Mr. and Mrs. William (Mary), 1969-1976 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Burd, Mr. and Mrs. Rick (Karen), 1995 September-December (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Burden, Mr. and Mrs. William (Peggy), 1959-1976 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Burke, Anna, 1967-1974 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Burr, Mary and Thompson, Dorothy, 1960 September-October (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Burnes, Richard Jr., 1992 January-April (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Bush, President and Mrs. George H. W. (Barbara), 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Butcher, Mr. and Mrs. Willard (Carole), 1974-1994 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Butler, Dr. Katherine, 1974-1989 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Byard, Mr. and Mrs. Spencer (Margaret - "Maggie"), 1972-1996 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - "B" Miscellaneous, 1957-1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - "B" Miscellaneous, 1976-1988 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - "B" Miscellaneous, 1989-1996 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Cabot, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas (Virginia)(Louis - son of TC), 1966-1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Cahn, Mrs. and Mrs. Miles (Lillian), 1994 March-December (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Calder, Alexander, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Calder, Alexander Jr. and III, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Cameron, Dr. Harlow, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Campbell, Mr. and Mrs. Colin (Nancy), 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Caraballo, Octavio, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Carden, Mr. and Mrs. George (Connie), 1955-1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Carmen, Albert, 1977-1992 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Carnegie, Lady Carmen, 1978-1996 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Carter, Mr. and Mrs. Dwight (Alice), 1973-1987 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Carter, President Jimmy, 1978 April (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Casals, Mr. and Mrs. Pablo (Marte), 1960 October-November (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Casey, Peggy, 1980-1995 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Cataldo, Richard ("Richie"), 1971-1993 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Chafee, Sen. John H., 1977 August 25 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Chan, Sou (House of Chan), 1961-1966 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Chapin, Schuyler, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Charney, Robert, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Chasin, Mr. and Mrs. Richard (Laura), 1974-1990 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Chatfield, Mr. and Mrs. A.H.(Marion), 1976-1992 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Chevallier, Robert (Sophie - daughter), 1976-1990 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Cheston, Charles, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Cheyne, Pierre, 1950-1978 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Cisneros, Mr. and Mrs. Gustavo (Patty), 1986-1995 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Clark, George, 1962-1996 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Clark, Walter E., 1963-1977 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Clarke, Mr. and Mrs. Bert (Wing), 1975-1992 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Coelho, Tony, 1989 June (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Cole, John N., 1972-1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Coleman, Mr. and Mrs. Paul (Ami), 1990 January-September (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Coman, Mr. and Mrs. Dale (Mona), 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Conger, Clemen, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Connolly, Sybil, 1971-1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Cook, Mr. and Mrs. Howard (Diane), 1973-1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Cooley, George R., 1976-1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Cooney, Joan Ganz, 1980-1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Cort, Mr. and Mrs. Stewart (Alys), 1988-1994 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Cox, Tom A., 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Creel, Mr. and Mrs. Dana (Jane), 1974-1979 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Crofoot, David and Dr. Michael, 1963-1992 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Cronkite, Walter, 1985-1993 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - "C" Miscellaneous, 1956-1978 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - "C" Miscellaneous, 1979-1995 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Daisey, Joyce, 1979 January-June (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Dana, Mr. and Mrs. A. Fairfield ("Fair")(Elizabeth), 1963-1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Dana, Mr. and Mrs. Richard (Nina), 1969-1980 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Davidson, Joan, 1991-1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Davidson, Mr. and Mrs. Spencer (Margaret), 1988-1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Davisson, Mr. and Mrs. Farrell, 1978 January-October (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Dayton, Joan, 1959-1966 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - de Bullrich, Mr. and Mrs. A. L., 1976 January-February (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - de Fortabat, Amalita, 1985-1989 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - de la Dehesa, Mr. and Mrs. Guillermo, 1987-1995 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - de la Renta, Mr. and Mrs. Oscar (Annette), 1988 January (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - De Larrocha, Alicia, 1969-1992 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Del Pozzo, Ralph, 1990 May (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - DeNormandie, Mr. and Mrs. Philip (Tina), 1971-1994 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - DePew, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas (Noel), 1979-1992 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - DeRose, Countess Yvonne, 1952-1992 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - DeRose Family, 1961-1964 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - DeRosen, Baron Leon and Baroness Olga (Michel - son), 1975-1985 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Desmarais, Mr. and Mrs. Paul (Jackie), 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Dickinson, Barry, 1994 March-August (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Diecidue, Mr. and Mrs. Joseph (Grace), 1985-1994 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Dietel, Mr. and Mrs. William (Linda), 1979-1995 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Dillon, Mr. and Mrs. Douglas (Suzzie), 1961-1994 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Dillon, Mr. and Mrs. Valentine (Helen), 1985-1990 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Dilworth, Mr. and Mrs. J. Richardson ("Dick")(Bunny), 1956-1996 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Dintenfass, Terry, 1972 March-May (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Diserins, Mr. and Mrs. Robert (Helen), 1973-1989 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Donawick, William and Melinda (daughter), 1979-1994 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Donnelly, Robert F., 1989-1995 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Douglas-Hamilton, Lady James (Susie)(James)(Andrew - godson), 1979-1995 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Douglass, Mr. and Mrs. Robert (Linda), 1980-1989 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Dowling, Betsey, 1993 January-February (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Dulles, Mr. and Mrs. John (Eleanor) (Ellen - daughter), 1979-1995 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - "D" Miscellaneous, 1954-1986 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - "D" Miscellaneous, 1987-1996 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Eastman, Joel W., 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Edwards, Mr. and Mrs. Agustin ("Doonie")(Malu), 1944-1996 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Ehrnrooth, Mr. and Mrs. Goran (Louise), 1972-1978 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Emory, Mr. and Mrs. Benjamin (Judy), 1974-1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Emory, Mr. and Mrs. German (Katherine), 1972-1994 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Enders, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas (Gaetana), 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Erikson, Gordon, 1973-1976 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Espinosa Yglesias, Angeles, 1978-1993 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Ethridge, Damaris, 1993 January (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Evans, Dr. James, 1991 June-July (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - "E" Miscellaneous, 1956-1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Fairfax, Lady Mary, 1972-1988 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Fayerman, Severin, 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Fenn, Richard, 1977-1990 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Fernald, Allen, 1986 July-August (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Farreira, Mr. and Mrs. Alexandre (Thereza), 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Ferrer, Marian, 1984-1990 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Few, Russell, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Fisher, Mr. and Mrs. Pieter (Ann), 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Flanders, Reginald, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Fleischman, Mr. and Mrs. Rick (Jennifer "Jen"), 1992-1996 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Florian, David, 1978-1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Forbes, Malcolm S., 1978-1994 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Fonteyn deArias, Dame Margot, 1984-1989 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Ford, President Gerald R. and Mrs. Ford (Betty), 1980 August 18 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Fortune, Mr. and Mrs. Robert (Liz), 1990-1996 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Foulke, Mr. and Mrs. William (Louisa), 1972-1993 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Franchetti, Baronessa Anne, 1990-1996 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Francolini, Mr. and Mrs. Emilio (Silvia), 1980-1991 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Franklin, Mr. and Mrs. George (Helene - "Benjy"), 1958-1994 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Fraser, The Honorable Malcolm, 1986 February-March (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Fraser, Dr. Richard, 1985-1995 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Freeman, Nancy, 1979-1986 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Frye, Clayton W. Jr. "Wes", 1976-1994 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Fujino, Yuriko, 1972-1980 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Fuller, Buckminster, 1973-1978 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Fung, Lady Ivy and Nelly and Kenneth Fung, 1973-1978 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Funk, Constance, 1988 April-July (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - "F" Miscellaneous, 1946-1995 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Gardmier, Mr. and Mrs. Camp (Comfort), 1965-1994 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Garland, Agnes, 1974-1980 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Gaspardo, Jean, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Gates, Perry, 1975-1978 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Gearhart, G. David, 1990-1995 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Geyelin, Mr. and Mrs. Henry ("Harry")(Fran), 1974-1995 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Gibbs, Mr. and Mrs. Arthur (Evelyn), 1973-1996 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Gibbs, Rachel ("Gibby"), 1949-1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Gilbert, Susanna, 1995 January-February (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Gillies, Paula, 1993 October-November (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Glidden, Mr. and Mrs. Fred (Priscilla), 1990-1995 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Goldberger, Paul, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Gommi, Barbara, 1984-1996 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Gonzalez, Mrs. and Mrs. Xavier (Ethel), 1972-1979 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Good, John M., 1971-1989 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Good, Merrie, 1971-1988 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Goodman, Benny, 1977 May (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Greenall, John, 1980-1995 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Gregorian, Vartan ("Greg"), 1985-1989 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Grierson, Ronald ("Ronnie"), 1972 April-June (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Griffin, Helen, 1959-1975 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Grant, Lady Katherine, 1993-1996 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Growald, Paul, 1989-1995 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Growald, Ursula, 1986 April-May (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Gunther, Jack Jr. ("Jay"), 1966-1986 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Guyton, Samuel, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Gyllenhammar, Mr. and Mrs. Pehr (Christina), 1974-1996 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - "G" Miscellaneous, 1972-1995 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Hajouji, Abou, 1972-1987 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Hall, Caryl, 1990-1994 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Hall, Robert G., 1975 June-October (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Hall, Thomas Steele, 1979-1988 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Hallinan, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas (Janet), 1985-1987 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Hammer, Dr. Armand, 1980-1990 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Hanes, Philip Jr., 1975-1994 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Hare, Montgomery ("Monty"), 1972-1995 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Harper, Mary H.J., 1989-1994 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Harriman, Mrs. W. Averell (Pamela), 1980 April 28 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Harris, Elin, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Harte, Mr. and Mrs. Edward (Janet), 1985-1996 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Haupt, Enid, 1992 October (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Hawton, Mr. and Mrs. Raymond (Elise), 1972-1989 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Heath, The Rt. Hon. Edward, M.P., 1966-1970 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Heckrath, Joan, 1955 September-October (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Heckscher, Mr. and Mrs. August (Claude), 1955-1995 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Heinz II, Mr. and Mrs. Henry ("Jack")(Drue), 1975-1986 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Heiskell, Marian, 1973-1979 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Henry, Mr. and Mrs. Berklie ("Buz")(Margaret), 1960-1965 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Herzberg, Harald, 1972-1980 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Hesse, HRH Princess Margaret of, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Hettling, Catherine, 1989-1991 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Hewitt, Mr. and Mrs. Alexander ("Sandy") (Bonnie), 1986-1996 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Hewitt, Mr. and Mrs. William (Tish), 1972-1996 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Hicks, Billie, 1975-1986 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Higgins, Betty, 1993 July (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Higgins, Mr. and Mrs. George ("Bud")(Kaye), 1979-1994 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Hildreth, Mr. and Mrs. Horace ("Willie")(Heddy), 1984 February (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Hillman, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas (Shelby), 1980-1992 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Hinckley, Mr. and Mrs. Robert (Tina), 1984-1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Hinshaw, Lillias, 1973-1980 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Hirschfield, Ira, 1990 May-July (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Hitterdal, D.M., 1984 January-August (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Hobbs, Genevra ("Ginnie"), 1974 July-August (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Hoegh, Mr. and Mrs. Leif (Lucy), 1961-1978 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Hoff, John K., 1977-1980 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Hohenlohe, Furstin Albrecht ("Sissy"), 1954-1979 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Holm, Mr. and Mrs. Steve (Sherry), 1992-1996 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Homer, Mr. and Mrs. Donald (Mary), 1978-1996 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Hood, Dean Lamartine, 1988 June-July (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Hooper, John, 1979-1992 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Horluchi, Paul, 1973 January-April (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Horne, Douglas, 1985-1992 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Houghton, Arthur A. Jr., 1978 January-March (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Howard, The Hon. Mrs. Henry (Del), 1973-1978 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Howe-Snow, Lucia, 1946-1995 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Howell, Mary, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Hudson, Mrs. Fitzgerald (Susan), 1990 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Hussey, Marmaduke and Lady Susan, 1988-1993 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Hyde, Anne, 1973-1995 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Hyde, Bryden Bordley, 1980-1996 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - "H" Miscellaneous, 1961-1972 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - "H" Miscellaneous, 1973-1985 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - "H" Miscellaneous, 1986-1995 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Ingersoll, Mr. and Mrs. Jared (Agnes), 1974-1995 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Ingraham, Jackie, 1994 January (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Iselin, Mr. and Mrs. John Jay (Lea), 1987-1990 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - "I" Miscellaneous, 1974-1992 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Jay-Carroll, Katherine, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Jejeebhoy, Lady Jamsetjee ("Soonoo"), 1970-1975 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Jessup, Pamela Rusell, 1974-1995 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Johnson, Mr. and Mrs. Belton (Patsy), 1972-1989 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Johnson, Philip, 1965-1994 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Johnson, Mrs. J. Lee (Ruth), 1971-1974 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Jordan, Ina, 1972-1995 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - "J" Miscellaneous, 1960-1996 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Kaiser, Mrs. Sylvia, 1958-1992 (Box 18, Folder 1)